MUHAMAD PARHAN MAULANA

Fullstack Developer (Javascript)

+6283836319218 | mparhanmaulana17@gmail.com

www.handev.my.id

SUMMARY

A programmer who can create software from various aspects, including web frontend, backend, and mobile. Experienced for over 1 year in this field and has completed 10+ real projects as well as personal projects using a full JavaScript tech stack.

EDUCATION

2021 - 2024 SMK YASBAM KOTA BOGOR

Teknik Komputer Dan Jaringan

WORK EXPERIENCE

2022 - 2023 | Internship | Pusat Pengembangan ASN

2023 - Now | Freelance

- Web and application development. Utilizing React.js, Next.js, React Native, or WordPress.
- Feature addition, debugging.

SKILLS

- · HTML, CSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- TYPESCRIPT
- REACT JS
- NEXT JS

- NODE JS
- EXPRESS JS
- MYSQL
- MONGODB
- FIREBASE
- SUPABASE

PORTOFOLIO

- · www.fashiotrendz.handev.my.id
- · www.threads.handev.my.id
- more: www.handev.my.id